Althernatively,it has also been suggested that some animals strand accidentally by following their prey ashore in the confusion of the chase.
另外也有人认为一些动物是在追逐猎物到岸上的混乱中意外搁浅。
In 1995 David Thurston monitored pilot whales that beached after following squid ashore.
1995年，大卫·瑟斯顿监控到巨头鲸在追踪岸边的鱿鱼后搁浅。
However,this idea does not seem to hold true for the majority of mass strandings
然而，这种想法并不适用于大多数大规模的搁浅，
because examination of the animals' stomach contents reveal that most had not been feeding as they stranded.
因为当检查搁浅的动物时，发现多数动物的胃里没有食物。
There are also some new theories which link strandings to huamns.
还有一些新理论将搁浅与人类相连。
A growing concern is that loud noises in the ocean cause strandings.
海洋噪音引发搁浅日益受到人们的关注。
Noises such as those caused by military exercises are of particular concern and have been pinpointed as the cause of some strandings of late.
例如军事演习的噪音特别受到关注，而且作为一些搁浅的原因被指出。
One of these,a mass stranding of whales in 2000 in the Bahamas coincided closely with experiments using a new submarine detection system.
其中一个发生在2000年的巴哈马群岛，一次大规模的鲸鱼搁浅与新型水下探测系统的实验同时发生。
There were several factors that made this stranding stand out as different from previous strandings.
有一些因素表明这次搁浅与以往的搁浅不同。
This led researchers to look for a new cause.
这让研究人员开始寻找新的原因。
For one,all the stranded animals were healthy.
首先，所有搁浅的动物都很健康。
In addition,the animals were spread out along 38 kilometres of coast,
另外，动物在海岸上散布了38公里，
whereas it's more common for the animals to be found in a group when mass strandings occur.
然而当大规模搁浅发生时，动物往往是成群的被发现。
A final theory is related to group behaviour,
最后一个理论与团体行为有关，
and suggests that sea mammals cannot distinguish between sick and healthy leaders, and will follow sick leaders,even to an inevitable death.
海洋哺乳动物不能区分生病和健康的领导者，它们会跟随患病的领导者，即使是导致一场不可避免的死亡。
This is a particularly interesting theory since the whales that are thought to be most social - the toothed whales - are the group that strand the most frequently.
这是一个很有意思的理论，因为鲸鱼（齿鲸）被认为是最爱群居的动物，它们最频繁的成群搁浅
The theory is also supported by evidence from a dolphin stranding in 1994.
1994年海豚的搁浅也证实了这个理论。
Examination of the dead animals revealed that apart from the leader, all the others had been healthy at the time of their death.
检查动物的死尸时发现，除了领导者以外，其他所有动物在死时都很健康。
Without one consistent theory however it is very hard for us to do anything about this phenomenon except to assist animals where and when we can.
然而，没有一个统一的理论很难让我们改变这个现象，除了帮助那些我们在何时何地发现的动物。
Stranding networks have been established around the world to aid in rescuing animals and collecting samples from those that could not be helped.
全世界成立了搁浅网络，旨在救助动物并从那些无法获救的动物身上提取样本。
I recommend John Connor's Marine Mammals Ashore as an excellent starting point
我推荐约翰·康纳的“海洋哺乳动物上岸”作为一个极好的出发点，
if you're interested in finding out more about these networks, or establishing one yourself.
如果你们想找到更多这方面的网络或建立自己的网络。